Diego Corradi

FRONT-END DEVELOPER



PROFILE

I am a Front-end Developer with almost one year of experience working in the field of Web.

In my free time I study web development topics, doing courses and make projects.

I'm ambitius and creative person, and at the same time, I want to learn and improve myself everyday.

My goal is to become the best version of myself.

CONTACT



+39 3408491706



diego.corradi95@gmail.com



https://diegocorradi.netlify.app



https://github.com/diecorra



@<u>diegocorradi</u>



Verona, Italy

EDUCATION

REACT ACADEMY - 74 hours IT Talent Factory, 2022 <u>Link course</u>

FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT - 191 hours start2impact, 2022 <u>Link course</u>

- Teacher: Platform e-learning with mentors
- · Front-end development student
- · React.js
- Javascript base 8 advance
- Html & Css

GIT FUNDAMENTALS - 4 hours Teacher Fabio Biondi, 2022 <u>Link course</u>

JS ES6 AND TYPESCRIPT FUNDAMENTALS - 3 hours Teacher Fabio Biondi, 2022 Link course

Diploma in IT, 2014 VILLAFRANCA DI VERONA

LANGUAGE

- Italian (Native)
- English (B1 Certificate)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer ARCHIVA S.R.L.
JAN 2022 - PRESENT

I manage implementations of new features and bug-fix.

I communicate with Back-End developer collegues for developping web applications. To create these applications, I use mainly Ext.js, JavasScript, HTML, CSS.

Also, for some projects I use React library.

I use Git as a tool versioning and BitBucket for repository hosting.

Software Developer

ARCHIVA S.R.L. FEB 2020 - DEC 2021

I have implemented an application for handling the warehouse of the company. To create this application, I used ASP,C#, HTML and CSS.

In the rest of the experience I made mainly bug-fixes in Java projects. I used SVN as a tool versioning.

ICT Developer

ARCHIVA S.R.L. JUN 2018 - JAN 2020

- Management of ETL/DWH/BI application development
- Software: Informatica Data Transformation Studio and Altova MapForce for mapping source system data (xml files, flat files, csv, edifact) to data warehouse tables
- Knowledge basic of SQL Server, Oracle, DB2, MariaDB for SQL programming

IOT Research and Development

EDALAB S.R.L. DEC 2016 - OCT 2017

- Project for University of Verona
- IoT Project: the use of Lorawan technology for communication between gateways and sensors

HOBBIES

- Running, I'm a marathoner
- Travelling
- Hiking
- Reading books on personal growth
- Creating front-end projects

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- React.js